[{"answer": "What I was struck by most, Piers, is how remarkable it was that you have -- you know, running for president is about convincing the American people that you can be trusted to do what you say you're going to do.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Did you like what you heard from the two candidates?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "The president spent a lot of time working throughout the administration to figure out a way to deal with a very, very difficult issue.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "So what's the difference?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well, clearly the governor embraced the strong and decisive policies that the president over the last three and a half years, but if you follow, and I know you have, Piers, the campaign, the 20 debates the Republicans have, Governor Romney staked out far, far, far more conservative positions on a whole host of issues, including Osama bin Laden.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "There were details on various things but in terms of a strategy, I thought they were pretty similar, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "I'm doing well.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "It's important to remember what he said.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Have the Republicans got a problem because of that op-ed piece that Mitt Romney wrote basically distancing himself from a bailout?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "No, I wasn't, unfortunately.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "But then if you were watching Letterman last night, Mr. Speaker -- were you?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, I was with Richard Branson recently, the head of Virgin Airlines, who in fact is building a system that next summer is going to take people up into near space, near orbit.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Do you take it at face value?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, funny enough, my brother is a British army colonel.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "I mean, what are we going to do with them?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Never seen them used in action?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "And he talked about education and he talked about the importance of gender equality.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "What would the odds have been on that, a Republican candidate mentioning peace 12 times to a Democratic president, zero?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Yes, I think he did.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Did he achieve that aim?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, in defense of Ante, he -- I mean he says that it might go Romney's way but he still says 70 percent chance that Obama will be re-elect.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What is your -- what is your sense of what's really happening in the battleground areas in particular?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I think that it will come down to Ohio.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "What is your gut feeling for the battleground battle in particular?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "You keep asking me who the real Mitt Romney is.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Isn't he much less threatening?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "-- very different argument to say that someone is not qualified to hold office.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "What about what Hillary Clinton said about Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Raising taxes -- wait, I assume your candidate, from your columns, is Barack Obama.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Who is my candidate?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "I am saying --", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Are you not an Obama supporter?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "You want to go ahead, Bissinger, or you want to let me finish?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I absolutely hear people saying that they are proud of the things --", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "And if you don't, has he really earned the right to be re-elected?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "I think on the whole, yes.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Do you believe he's done a great job in totality?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, the reason I did it -- and it's a personal choice, and I respect what Charles -- what his decision is.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "What have you sensed in yourself about the choices in front of you that made you do that?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "I think it reflects the fact the country's gone to a volunteer force.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "What do you think of that, General Clark?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "You know, we had a million men in France.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Well, I think to a great extent, it still leaves a lot of people concerned that the administration felt so necessary to get out and make pronouncements about what turned out to be false facts on the ground.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "How important was it from your eyes?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "I think it was a strategic move.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Were you pleased by what you heard from him?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "That certainly may be the perception in Great Britain.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Do you think that's a fair assessment, that Obama, for all his critics, has in four years done a very different kind of style?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "We need a winning strategy.", "docId": "121023pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Or is the answer that we need less going forward?", "qSentId": 598}]